Did you think we abandoned you?
Or that we'd run out of magic? Well, think again, ladies and gentlemen,
because you are about to be amazed.
If you're here right now, then you have followed the clues and cracked the
code. Congratulations and welcome.
It's been 10 years since the Horsemen last appeared, but we are back.
Okay, so come in close.
Closer. Because the more you think you see, the easier it'll be to dress up
old tricks and fool you that they are new.
So, my name is J.
Daniel Atlas.
And allow me to speak, as I often do for my less charismatic colleagues,
when I say it is very good to be back.
Yes, yes, we vanished for a while.
But in the world of magic, everything that disappears reappears.
Well, at least if the trick is done right.
I'm Mayor McKinnon.
Unlike my very good buddy here, Danny, most of you checked your egos at the
door tonight.
You found this little underground soiree because you wanted to get fooled.
Hey, everyone, I'm Jack Wilder.
Ward Pandemics.
Climate change.
AI, let's face it.
We all need magic more than ever.
I want you to pay very close attention.
You are not gonna want to miss this next trick.
Henley Reeves.
Now, Henley Reeves Scanlan.
Three kids, two dogs, and a master's degree.
It's been a while.
Did you miss us?
You guys were great.
Back in the.
I used to want to be a magician.
Then I turned 12.
Careful. They might be listening.
Ooh, I'm shaking in my.
All Saints.
What are they going to do? Is that real gold? What? Is that real gold? Yeah.
I'm rich.
This is a magic show, dude.
Every fool here is a pickpocket, or pickpocket's fool.
Was that a haiku? What was that? Each of you just received a playing card.
If you wouldn't mind pulling it out.
Great. Now, we're gonna shuffle the deck so everybody find a random person
near them and switch cards with them.
And then when you've done that, find somebody else and switch with them.
Okay? Great.
Now, you there.
Down there.
Yep. What is your card? Ace of diamonds.
Ace of diamonds.
Okay, let's make things a little more complicated here.
Does anybody else here have the ace of diamonds meets me? Ace of diamonds.
Oh, looks like we have a fifth horseman, not named Lula, come up on stage.
You're gonna be our helper.
Now, look into my eyes and sleep.
Still got it.
Now, this might look an ordinary kid to you, but tonight he is going to do
extraordinary magic.
Like a man possessed.
Literally. Henley? Yes, Mary? Would you mind stepping Inside his body? Yep.
And, Jack, why don't you throw yourself on in there, too? What I do best.
And, oh, God help you, Atlas, why don't you slither on inside as well? And I
might as well wedge myself in there, too.
It takes a village to make magic.
J. Daniel Atlas in the house.
So, who wants to see a magic trick?
Take it away, Merit.
Hello, you beautiful people.
Now, everyone knows that merit McKenna reads minds.
Well, now I'm him or he's me.
Who knows? I'm sensing someone came here tonight not to enjoy magic, but to
tear it down.
Is there a Brett Finnegan in the house?
Now, you and your friends here set up the camp Hobart crypto exchange.
Took the good people of New York's employee pension and welfare fund half
its cash.
You're rounding up.
And also, the risks were laid out very clearly.
Everybody knew what they were getting into.
Dude, did you hide the profits offshore? Count ending in 5, 3, 2, 9, 7.
You couldn't know that without my.
Oh, is this real gold? Rhett, you ought to be more careful with your things,
man. Amerit's a psychic.
But me, Jack, I'm in the sleight of hand.
Ask your friends.
They've just done their part to close the wealth gap.
Now, here's a little redistribution.
Thank you.
Fire up, dude.
I'll kick your ass.
Oh, someone forgot Henley can fly.
We can take it from here, But a round of applause for the best sportsman on
stage.
Fantastic. So, everybody, I want you to take your drink and I want you to
pour it onto the face of your card.
Can you do that? Those 12 unique words on each of your cards form the
password to your new crypto wallet.
Oh. Log on and you'll find Brent's stolen millions more fairly
redistributed. Oh, my God.
50. 50,000 bucks.
50,000,
you're freaking done, dude.
Cool your head, gingerbread, cuz I am having a vision.
Maybe cops are going to come bursting through that door to perform a magic
trick of your own.
And disappear in 3, 2, 1.
Now, come in close.
Closer. Because the more you think you see, the easier it'll be to dress up
old tricks and fool you that they are new.
Oh, my God.
No,
look, in my opinion, I think you did a great job.
I think my atlas was good.
My merit could probably use some work.
It's like San Diego stoner and a shrimp boat captain out of Vegas.
Sure. No, seriously, Bosco, I don't know how you do it.
A good impersonation isn't just about the mimicry it's about attention to
detail, personality and nuance.
Okay, okay.
Let me try.
I am J.
Daniel. Alex.
The closer you look, the less you see.
There's something.
Yep. You'll work on it.
It wasn't bad.
It's a good start, but could use some work.
Sure. What do you keep looking at? Nothing.
Cheer up, guys.
Come on, look at us.
Look at how far we've been.
Totally scored tonight.
All right, next time, you wear the pink wig, okay? No, dude, it's locked
again. Okay, I'll pick it.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Do the thing.
No. Please, do the thing.
It's so cool.
I'll hold your back.
So unnecessary.
It's fun.
Hey,
you got this.
She's like a little Mario.
She is like Mario.
Careful, careful.
You okay? Yeah.
If I could do that, I would only do that.
So cool.
It's insane.
Happy? Yeah.
That was awesome.
Please let us in.
It's cold.
Best apartment in the whole city.
Yup. And no one will ever see it but us.
Such a shame.
That guy is so screwed.
Who's rich now? Charlie, can you turn that thing off, please? I think I've
had enough Atlas for one night.
Yeah, I gotcha.
Bosco, can you check for pizza? I'm so hungry.
Me, too.
No pizza.
But we got beer and.
No, literally, just beer.
Any takers? Yeah, I'll have one.
Dude, seriously, turn that thing off.
I did.
Okay, real funny, guys.
Where's the other projector? I'm not a hologram.
I'm not a hologram.
Right. Yes, exactly what a hologram would say.
Oh, my God, you're real.
Never touch my face again.
I'm so sorry.
I thought that you were a hologram.
I would never do that.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
How are you? How did you find us? I don't know.
Took me about 30 seconds.
And if it was this easy for me to find you, how hard would it be for the
police? Well, hold on.
The police? Yeah, the police.
Why would the police be looking for us? I don't know.
What about that little heist you just pulled? Or the fact that you're
squatting in this place so that your electricity comes from the circuit box
in the corner? I don't know.
It could be anything.
Am I right, Bozo? Bosco.
Bosco Leroy.
That's right.
Yeah, Bosco Leroy.
What did you type fictional magician name into? ChatGPT? Oh, that's actually
my real name.
Atlas. Would your mom have sex with a map? That's not funny.
You don't know anything about us? Dude, I know everything about you.
The dubiously named Bosco Laroi, promising acting career cut short by
crippling student loans.
It's a bummer you had to drop out of Juilliard, but you never stopped
performing. If.
If memory serves, your last paid gig, I think, was dressing as Elmo in Times
Square. First of all, I have the number.
Elmo the Red Teletubby.
Po. The Red Teletubby.
Her name is Po.
She's my favorite one.
Her name is Poe.
Cute. And you, June McClair, kicked out of every boarding school your
parents forced you to attend.
Not a big fan of authority, I take it.
Let me guess.
You think the olds broke the planet, and it's your generation's duty to
clean up their mess.
Am I right? Am I wrong? No.
And so you ran away from home, made your way to New York, where you ran into
this guy at Tannen's Magic Shop.
Charlie Geese.
Yeah, hi.
I actually couldn't find a lot about you online.
Although I do know you were an orphan.
I knew you were in and out of foster care your entire childhood and that you
didn't know the meaning of family until you hooked up with these two.
And so the three of you have been working your little Robin Hood act for
years now, trying to change the world one trick at a time, all leading to
your riskiest theft to date.
My identity.
You were there.
You had our faces plastered on every scaffolding and subway stop in the
city. That's copyright infringement, by the way.
Of course I was there.
So, what'd you think? I think your merit needs work.
I knew it.
That's a sensitive topic.
You don't even get it.
But overall design was impressive.
And that's you, I assume.
The quiet guy.
Textbook behind the scenes.
Yeah, Alexander Herman.
He said that the people who designed his tricks were the real geniuses.
The fact that you know that man's name behind the scenes, clearly.
And you, your sleight of hand was advanced.
Good dexterity.
You're quick and nimble on your feet.
Really? I was impressed.
Thanks. You're welcome.
Sounds like we're pretty great.
You're far from it.
But maybe with a little fine tuning, you could be.
Yeah, I could.
I could see why the eyes sent me to you.
I'm sorry, did you say the Eye? Yeah, the Eye.
All right, listen.
This card arrived at my apartment three weeks ago, along with four plane
tickets and instructions hidden in the lining for a trick bigger and better
than anything you have ever seen.
A trick that, for some reason, includes the three of you.
Us? Why not the other Horsemen? The other Horsemen are dead.
What? To me? They're dead to me.
Stop interrupting.
No. Things got emotional.
Everyone quit.
I took a walk about in Australia.
It's a long story.
And now you need us.
According to that card, yes.
Well, we don't need you.
So, Bosco, what.
What do we need this guy for? We're crushing it.
You're crushing it? You're stealing a little money from some crypto, bro.
I am talking about big fish here, man.
I'm talking about something that will make a real difference.
I thought that's what you kids are all about.
It is.
No. Exactly.
Yes, we are.
Yeah. But I think we can catch our own fish.
You can? No.
No. Good luck with that.
What? No.
Can you just wait one second? What are you doing? What's.
What's going on? Are you out of your mind? Mind bling.
This is J.
Daniel Atlas.
Yeah, I know who he is.
He's a freaking legend.
He was a legend.
Now he's just kind of a dick.
Can you.
Sure, Bosco, he is kind of a dick, but he is a horseman.
I mean, come on.
Just trust us on this.
Please. Okay.
Decision time, kids.
What's it going to be? Are you in or are you out?
What's the trick?
Welcome esteemed community members, valued press friends and colleagues.
We are gathered here tonight to celebrate Vanderburg's latest and greatest
mind. C3.
Or as we like to call her, Mahle Zulu, for the beautiful one.
Because every child is beautiful in the eyes of its mother.
Our customer can rest assured that when they buy the world's greatest symbol
of love, that it was produced with nothing but.
Welcome. Thank you all so much for making the trip out here.
Now, I take it you were all impressed by Amal.
Sorry, C3.
Oh, it's quite dramatic.
But I also understand that you have chosen this fine day to broach some
concerns which, contrary to your expectations, I don't begrudge.
Fire away.
Right. Well, the board field set projections might be optimistic with
increasing competition from lab grown and in the event, borrowing rates.
William, my father loved you.
But there was a reason he called you his dark cloud.
Oh, shame the Vanderburgh family does not lose.
As you're well aware, our motorsports team just won the Monaco championship
for the seventh time.
The man will produce.
Yes. Next, right? Pricing the minimums that you've set.
Will you humor me, William, in a demonstration about reality? This diamond
is, say what, 35 carats the AWDC would price it at US$3 million.
William, will you open your mouth and stick out your tongue? Now.
Really. Really.
Now, if William here were to swallow it, that selfsame diamond would tear
his throat to shreds.
He would bleed to death before paramedics arrived.
So, to the AWDC, it's 3 million.
But to William, priceless.
Tell me then, as the CEO responsible for the world's last great diamond
mines, should I undercut our profits or should I choose prices that I know
our unique clients will pay?
As I thought.
Now, unless there are more concerns, I would like to head to Antwerp with my
price list and show off our stones.
Oh, you know, you probably could have led with free trip to Europe.
You know, little known fact about Antwerp.
Oh, great, more magic trivia.
This is fun.
No, just going to say that they make great biscuits.
Oh, do they? Can we actually get some, please, On Atlas, obviously.
No, no, I'm not getting you biscuits.
I just got you chocolates.
Okay, all right, listen, this is not a vacation, okay? We have three days to
prepare an effect that'll make your barely passable peppers Ghost Rift look
like a cave painting.
All right, come here.
The Heart Diamond.
The most valuable jewel in history and the foundation of the Vanderburg
Mining Corporation.
Now, for years, the families kept this big rock hidden inside their secret
vault, 70 stories underground.
And not just any ground.
The Arabian desert.
No one beyond.
Their most trusted team has been inside access through a single elevator,
constantly monitored by armed guards,
and behind a multi level biometric security system.
But the world will be watching.
Because for the first time in half a a century, that diamond is being
traveled here to Antwerp to establish credibility and to spur bidding at a
private auction for the company's latest finds in three days time.
Okay, obviously I'm down for stealing, but what makes this diamond so
special? Oh, because the magical Tarot card told us to.
J. Right.
Okay, that's very cute, but can I please finish? You don't finish.
Jeez, you've been talking forever.
Yes, and I'm about to talk more, so please pay attention.
For decades, first Peter Vandenberg, now his daughter Veronica, have been
selling these diamonds at inflated prices to arms dealers, traffickers,
warlords the world over to like, help launder their money.
So, I mean, the cash is dirty.
I mean, in some cases it's like literally blood soaked.
But then, voila, it's cleaned.
In exchange for these precious stones, she makes all the world's worst
people possible.
So whoever sent that tarot card are the few truly honorable people left in
this world.
The only people that still care about justice.
The people I haven't spoken to in a long time, they call themselves the Eye.
And they want us to do something that the Horsemen never could.
This man.
This is a chance to drive a stake through the heart of the devil herself.
Let's do it.
All eyes will be on me and the Heart tonight at the auction.
I have to look dazzling.
Do you have that kitten? Kiss.
Color.
The tower.
Yes. Straw.
Who's that? British photographer from Vanity Fair.
What's his name again? Mark.
Mark Scriber.
Schreiber. Good God.
Confirm him.
Cancel the others.
We went wide last year.
This year.
Exclusivity. All right, we're open.
Transparent. We have nothing to hide.
Okay, perfect.
I'll have it done.
This is Veronica.
Hush, little baby, don't say a word.
Who is this?
How did you get this number?
This is a private line.
And that was a bit tone deaf.
I asked who you are.
Veronica. The storage unit to your left.
Look familiar? That belonged to that boy who died 15 years ago.
This means nothing to me.
Or anyone, really.
You and I both know what you did.
Look, if you have real evidence and you're out to get me, why not just use
it? Fifteen years ago, you took what your father loved most.
Now I'm going to do the same to you.
I want the hot diamond.
You're going to give it to me or I'm going to hold up a looking glass for
the whole world to see you as you are.
Go ahead.
I have nothing to hide.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry about that.
Hi. Can you help me find this? I've been looking for, literally for an hour.
Yes, it's going to be right over there.
Ma'. Am.
Mark Schreiber.
James Wynn Vanderberg.
Pr. Huge admirer of your work, James.
What about Danny? Oh, Danny.
Yet, sadly, we had to let her go.
Turns out she was racist.
And also she booked you into the Radisson Blue in a partial view.
Double, thankfully.
I took the liberty of moving you to the front.
I do not lef.
Yes, the residential suite is befitting of, well, presidents and talented
photographers like yourself.
Your gal invitation has been rerouted.
If I could just check your confirmation.
Thank you.
I also bumped your shoe from 7 to 9pm to give you proper time to make your
magic. Someone gets it.
Take, for instance, diamonds created in laboratories.
They purport to have value, but they're neither natural nor red.
What honest woman wants a falsehood on her finger? One of the great truths
left is the power behind a natural Gem.
Real diamonds fill people with passion.
As they have four centuries.
That's right.
In fact, Marie Antoinette wore the hope diamond for a single day and a month
later was dragged to the guillotine by some very, as you say, passionate
folks. Marie Antoinette didn't die because of a diamond.
She died because of a monstrous lack of empathy.
Well, and truth is, she never even wore the hope.
People just believe she did.
Really? That's kind of interesting.
So it was not the mob that killed her.
And it was not the guillotine.
It was a story.
I must not know my own guest list.
Are you in the diamond business? No, no, I'm in the illusion business.
Like you see, for centuries diamonds were worthless until some very smart,
very rich people like Veronica here told us that not only are these little
shards of glass rare, but that no self respecting couple could possibly get
married without one.
No, that one is a good magic trick.
The problem with the trick is all the good ones have a little twist in the
tail. Is it you? This one? Me? Of course not.
No, no.
I mean you wouldn't have let me in had I not demonstrated the finest moral
fiber like some of your other guests.
I noticed Luis Preseno, the arms dealer over there.
Hello, sir.
And of course Maria Bortnik.
When starstruck how she manages to mingle while monopolizing her state
media. Perhaps you'd care to reveal yourself.
Then we can apply the same scrutiny to you.
Not just yet.
I'm sorry for interrupting.
That won't be necessary.
Let him eat cake.
Mark Schreiber.
Veronica Vanderburg.
Lets make this quick, shall we? Our auction begins shortly.
I trust you can do me and the heart justice.
Yes. I only have one rule.
What I say goes.
Well. I'm sure I can find my submissive side.
Well, if not, I'll find it for you.
Oh, I like you.
Right this way, darling.
I don't want to be too matte.
Sure, sure.
But I don't like the sides of my nose shining.
Show me.
Excuse me.
Can the little fruit fly in my shot please? Shoo, shoo, shoo.
Thank you.
The only thing more valuable than that diamond is my time.
I did my research on you.
Your industry, like mine, is besieged by manufacturer lore.
But you, you bring us beauty as it is.
We're alike in that regard.
We don't sell contrivance, we sell reality.
Well, I would argue that we don't sell at war.
Others buy.
See
the diamond.
Take it out.
I bo.
Absolutely not.
The glare in the glass from are the photos.
I don't tolerate imperfections.
I don't imagine someone is ravishing as Ms.
Vanderberg does either.
So take it out or find yourself a new photographer.
In truth, I was hoping you'd ask.
I don't remember asking.
There it is.
Beautiful. Working.
Fabulous. Fabulous.
Fabulous. Beautiful.
Yes. We're smiling.
We're having fun.
This is what we came for.
Hold it.
That's the money shot.
Hold it there.
And you, ma', am, are far enough.
I'm just trying.
I'm trying to help.
Her forehead is shinier than the diamond.
Do my job.
I don't get bored when it comes to the heart.
You listen to me.
Get. I can walk myself.
Thank you,
Mr. Schraer.
If you're all you purport to be, you should already have what you need.
More than enough.
Thank you.
Excellent.
Well, it's been a pleasure, but I have buyers waiting.
The hell? What happened? I don't know.
Turn signal.
Let's go.
At last, the auction we've all been waiting for.
Now, if you're here tonight, you probably think you've seen everything.
So it is to you that I ask everything.
It's not been seen in person for a quarter of a century.
Still the largest diamond ever discovered.
The Heart.
Congratulations to all of you.
And for getting away with it for so long.
Well, guess what? Climate change doesn't believe in you either.
You tore your fortunes from our Mother Earth, set fire to her skies and your
private jets.
Let her dry with your insatiable young man.
We all want to save the world here, but time is also precious, and you're
wasting mine.
Zip it, Sparkles.
Why don't you stop sucking on plastic straws and suck on this?
Honored guest.
My name is J.
Daniel Atlas.
You may remember me as your personal favorite of the Four Horsemen of Magic.
Now watch closely as I make the famous Heart diamond appear on my palm.
Gee whiz.
He must be as starved for attention as Greenpeace here.
Rest assured that the diamond is completely safe.
Is it, now? A wise man once told me in the mirror, in fact, never assume
you're the smartest person in the room.
Prove it.
Be my guest.
All right.
Well, let's see if we can get that case open.
Abracadabra. No.
Alakazam. Wait.
Open sesame.
Still safe with me.
Relax. Relax, Veronica.
Now, as your ads like to remind us, diamonds are forever.
Get to st.
Now you.
Stop him.
Jeff. Hey.
What are you doing here? Saving your ass.
You're welcome.
You got one too.
Hi. I'm June.
Yeah, who's she sorry.
She's with us.
I guess you guys don't care about the environment.
Stronger than you look.
Hey,
hey, hey, hey.
Stop. Don't get this in the way for fake a What now? My car just sent to get
you out of there.
I don't know.
Henley Reeves.
I had so many posters of you.
Okay, I fanboy later.
But it does, you know, it is really nice to see you.
Fanboy later.
We got to go up.
Put your hands up and.
This is some bullshit.
What is happening? Beethoven's Concerto in D Major Bullshit, bullshit,
bullshit. Mary.
What the hell was that? Atlas.
I would like to see you hypnotize three dudes in Belgian.
You mean Flemish? Okay, that explains it.
Lovely reunion.
We have to go.
Henley Reeves.
Welcome back.
Thanks. And may I say you are okay.
Come on, let's go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was paying her a compliment because it was nice to see her and only her.
We get it
up there.
Do you see any other people trying to escape?
Was in my hand the whole time.
It never.
They didn't swap the diamond.
They swapped the case.
And you are far enough.
Why don't you stop sucking on plastic straws and suck on this?
Open sesame.
Diamonds are forever the Tubbo.
Yes, ma'.
Am. We're going to make them regret this.
And then some.
Marks drive a Vanity Fair.
What did I miss?
You know, thought it'd be shinier.
Okay. All right.
Give it back.
Oh. Oh.
So slippery.
Heads up.
Okay, don't do that again.
Hey, can I address the infant in the room? Oh.
Who are these guys? These are the wonderful kids that deep faked our show.
What? Yeah.
You had the cops sent to my house.
You freaked out my kids.
Yeah, sorry.
Sorry about that.
How are the kids, though? How was the whole boring suburban life you left us
for? Hey, relax, man.
You missed your shot.
See the size of that rock? No.
Let me see that.
Oh. It's no hard diamond, but it's impressive.
I already told you, Danny.
I didn't feel safe trying to escape from a straight jacket hanging upside
down. I was six months pregnant.
Come on.
We would have flipped you right side up at the end.
You'd have been fine.
Come on.
You guys don't even miss me.
How long did it take you to replace me? An afternoon and the better part of
an evening.
Hey, speaking of, how is Boodle? Are you guys still.
No, she.
She moved to Paris.
I don't know.
She dumped the great J.
Wilder. My God.
I'm sorry.
My apologies.
Don't you need to be on some, like, cruise Ship somewhere humiliating
yourself. Humiliating myself? Yeah.
I make five figures per cruise.
Plus perks.
Plus perks, he said.
And I thought Merrick drinking himself to death in Mexico was depressing.
Ooh, speaking of, I gotta get back to it.
This liver's not gonna destroy itself.
Can we dry dock this thing? Wait, wait, wait.
You're leaving? Well, yeah.
I mean, great catching up.
I don't know what.
See you in another 10.
Nice to meet you, little task poles.
Adios. Yeah, you know what? Well, I'm out of here too.
I have a gig to get to.
Really? They covering your Uber? Signed an NDA.
Can't say a word.
What are you doing? Six handles, none of them opening.
Who do you think you're talking to? Oh, I'm sorry, but I don't really know
what's going on with you guys.
I'm getting the feeling there's a lot of weird history here and things are a
little awkward.
Yeah. You guys, you used to be the Horseman.
I don't get it.
Why did you break up? Ask them.
Ask them why we broke up.
If it was up to me, we wouldn't know
the Eye wanted us to expose a Russian arms dealer.
We really have to live through this.
We may some huge mistakes.
We got sloppy, cocky.
Because of us, Dylan Shrike will never see the outside of a Russian prison
again. Who? Dylan Shrike.
Okay? He's a Horseman.
Come on, do your homework, man.
I'm so sorry, guys.
I had no idea.
Why? He's stuck in there forever.
Which is obviously a tragedy and something I'll never forgive myself for.
Yeah, fine, man.
But it didn't mean you have to quit.
That is only a bummer, guys.
Sorry about that.
A bummer? I love the way your generation sums things up so eloquently.
I mean, someone explain to me why these prepubes are even here.
Same reason you are, man.
I wanted a heart.
Well, we got the heart.
What does the aisle want us to do next? No idea.
I know one thing, but you've got a half a billion dollar diamond in your
hands. They're gonna get in touch.
Yeah, probably.
Whoa, wait, wait.
Atlas, can I see your car? Yeah.
Wow. It's a map.
Hey, Atlas, it's your dad.
No, it's.
It's a map.
That only reveals itself when the Horsemen are together.
Bad chance.
Really, dude? I mean, come on.
The Eye obviously wants you guys to do this.
You're the Horseman.
Start acting like it.
All right.
I suppose Rosa Rito can wait a couple days.
I can try.
To reschedule this gig.
It's not gonna be easy, but I'll figure it out.
I mean, I have kind of missed running for my life and jumping up rooms with
you guys.
Guys. It's good to have you back.
Thanks. Okay, so where is this place?
What are we supposed to be doing here? The eye will let us know.
All right.
What are you doing? Taking a photo.
Please don't do that.
Post photos of the top secret location.
Want to be in it? I don't want to be in.
Could be used for.
For memories.
No, not memories.
Evidence.
Huh. I've never seen a door like this.
Okay. I can't open it.
You got this, Jack.
Wait. Don't you mean June? Jack's our lockpick.
Whoa. Looks like a little healthy competition.
Come on.
This isn't fair.
I've been picking locks since before she was born.
Let me find the keyhole.
Maybe the other side.
You're not inspiring confidence right now, Jack.
He's got it.
Feeling rusty.
Don't rush me.
When does he start the lock picking? Hey, Jack, I don't think this is a lock
you pick.
I think it's a lock you solve.
So
show them how it's done.
Oh, you mind if I just figure this out really quickly? Okay.
If you've ever done an escape room, you'd know there are all kinds of
different puzzles.
It's not just about locks and keys.
Whoa. Huh? You might want to update your game.
Hey, Jack.
Whoa. But by all means, lead the way.
I think he loosened it for her, ultimately.
Wow. Wow.
What is this place? Magic nerd heaven? P.T.
silver's coffin.
See, guys? Houdini's straight jacket.
Yes, it is.
Hey, can I put you in here for old time's sake? No.
No. I thought it was funny.
Thanks a lot.
You want to come in?
Charlie, check this out.
Dude. What is it? Bullet catch.
No way.
Yeah.
Dead end.
Yeah. Hey, guys.
Or is it?
Oh, my God.
Yeah, it is.
That's weird.
The die should be here.
The ball should be here.
Oh. Well played.
It's nothing.
Four rows.
1, 5, 8, 4.
Is it a code? 1, bucket, 1, 5 minus 4.
1584. The discovery of Witchcraft.
It's the first book on stage Magic is when it was published.
But how does he know that? He's basically a computer full of useless
information.
Useless?
This is cool.
Unreal. Nice.
Hey, guys.
It's the floor plan of the chateau.
But it's different somehow.
Up is down, left is right.
Even the rooms are drinks.
My horsemen.
Thaddeus so good to see you.
So good to see you.
Dad, can I just check the ring camera and buzz the sim? Now where's the fun
on that? Sir.
Hi, I'm Charlie.
I. I'm such a big fan of yours.
Hi, Charlie.
I've never seen a Luber lens this big in person.
Really? You ain't seen nothing yet.
So you sent the tarot cards? No, no.
I've long since given up such foolishness.
And your collective dysfunction? No, the only magic I do now is for my
grandchildren. Some weeks ago, however, a card did appear on my doorstep,
warning me to prepare this chateau for the arrival of seven soon to be
fugitives from the mall.
That tracks.
Yeah. Wait, so why does the Eye want us here? I can only assume that
whatever it is they want you to do next is hidden somewhere in these walls.
See this chateau? Chateau Roussillon used to be their home.
In 1943, the Allies needed military miracles from every source.
They enlisted the aid of some of the most talented magicians of the time.
They built a faux city using mud, cardboard, lights, thousands of inflatable
rubber tanks to misdirect the Germans.
The genius of Jasper Maskelyne.
Somebody knows his history.
Wait, so what do the Nazis have to do with the diamond? That I do not know.
But the answer is here somewhere.
We just have to start looking.
Ms. Vanderburg.
How do you respond to the rumors that your company is nothing but a front
for body laundry? The Horsemen are thieves posing as anti capitalist
entertainers. And they have unfairly targeted me and my good company.
I challenge anyone who maligns us to look closely at our operations and our
books. And I challenge police to put those magicians back where they belong
in the past.
All right, no more questions.
No more questions, please.
Thank you.
Enterprises. It was an inside job.
Thieves knew exactly where the blind spots were.
How's it.
Let me guess.
You're the one behind these Horsemen.
In their little stable hands.
No. Why would I ask for the diamond and then try to steal it? If I were you,
I'd figure out a way to get it back and fast.
I understand that you and your race team will be in Abu Dhabi later this
week. A perfect neutral ground.
I'll bring my evidence.
You bring your hearts.
If you have one.
Have you found them yet? We do have a few leads.
They were seen near the South Art of Belgium.
Now they're saying the Horsemen have been seen in France.
1 hour ago.
The head of the French police owes me.
Just call him and say that I want These Horsemen's heads served up on a
platter. The gendarme will find them.
You sure of it? Patty has told us to look for something.
What do you think it is?
Oh, wow.
This is cool.
You are not a big talker.
Oh, sorry.
But you are a big apologizer.
Sorry, I just did it again.
Sorry. I mean, I'm just nervous.
I. I'm.
I'm a big fan of you guys.
And I got the cops called up, and I'm really not gonna say it.
You're forgiven.
You guys make the Horseman look good.
If I didn't see you, why weren't you in it? Oh, I just.
I prefer to be behind the scenes.
You know, I design all of our tricks.
Where are we going? I feel like we're lost.
Do you really prefer that, or is that just something you hide behind? What
do you mean? Well, I.
Whoa. For years, I told myself I wanted to be an assistant.
I didn't mind being upstaged by Atlas because he's so brilliant.
But really, I just.
I was afraid.
I was afraid to take the spotlight.
Ooh. Thaddeus was right.
Up is down,
upside down room.
Cool. Cool Is nothing impressive to you.
That's why I said cool.
Do you not know what cool means? All right, let's just try to figure out how
this room works.
Okay? Yeah,
figured it out.
Of course.
That's right.
You know everything already.
So, what did I do wrong this time? Ah, nothing.
My apologies.
You're amazing.
It's an honor to watch you.
Has anyone ever told you that you're a control freak? Yep.
Many times.
Whoa. Hey.
I did figure it out.
Oh, wow.
Gummies kicked in.
I wonder what we're looking for.
Anything weird.
This is all weird.
Jesus, look at this.
You know, I have always looked up to you.
Oh, yeah? Yeah.
Before you became a cruise ship magician.
Hey, I also do corporate events.
Oh, no way.
I couldn't tell.
So that was a total waste.
What now? One trick, okay? No charm, no gift of gab.
Just one trick.
Dude, I do not have to prove myself to you.
I mean, you kind of do.
Show me why the Eye picked you.
You know what? Prove to me that you don't need a babysitter.
Oh, what now? You stop performing.
You're done showing off because your misfit friends aren't here.
They're my family.
Don't you dare.
I don't have to impress them.
All right, fine.
Forget it.
I just want to you tell.
See what you were capable of when you weren't trying to win cheap applause
But I guess the answer is nothing.
All right.
Want to see magic trick? See, the problem with you, Atlas, is that you just
like to over complicate things.
Man, it is a lot easier to find a diamond than you think.
And to make it disappear.
Nice. Check your pocket.
Really? Yeah.
Hmm, not bad.
Card to impossible location.
Don't play checkers on a chessboard because I'm already five steps ahead of
you. Check your pocket.
Hey, those are priceless antiques.
Yeah. This room is where old relics go to their final resting place.
Yep, you are.
You're probably right, Thaddeus.
But not before they have one last shot, I think.
Glory, what's going on here? Pretty good.
But you should try to do things a little more slow.
Really let your audience enjoy the real magic.
Okay. Wow.
Thanks. I've never been great at poker, but is a diamond trumped by a heart?
Oh, there it is.
Nice misdirection.
But let's not forget what this is really about.
Making a jewel disappear.
Let's see this one.
Keep your eye on the prize.
Round and round they go.
Where they stop, nobody knows.
Good as going.
Black art.
Table's rigged.
Saw it when I came in.
Time for a clean escape.
Oh yeah.
Where's he going? I know what he's doing.
Jack in the box.
That's a trick.
It's old stuff.
If I had known he was that easy to get rid of.
Not that easy.
Oh. Okay, enough of the warm up egg.
Time for the headliner.
I want you to think of one of these cards.
But don't think of the one you think I want you to think of.
Got one? Yeah, I got one.
What was your card? Four of hearts.
Oh, nice one, Professor.
I'm impressed.
Hey, hey.
That whiskey is older than you.
Sorry, boss.
So sorry.
Look you guys, I'm not gonna lie.
This is really cool.
Really, really cool.
Go show em.
But I think I just want to make it a little cooler.
No storm in China.
There we are.
Beautiful. I was red, white and winter.
Guys, Snow is rare in the this part of France.
But ice? That is just impossible.
How'd you do a vanish so good? Oh, magician never tells.
Check mate.
Face it, Bosca.
Wisdom and skill overcome youth and arrogance every time.
Thank you.
Never assume you're the smartest guy in the room.
Prove anything.
Give me a break, man.
You didn't prove anything.
Hey, can I just remind everyone we still haven't figured out why we're even
in this World War II relic.
Wait. Jasper.
Masculine. The.
The magician who vanquished the Nazis.
He built fake cities, fake tanks.
I mean, I wonder.
Whoa. Oh.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
I was right.
Hey, Magic 101, man.
Never act surprised when the trick actually works.
Sorry.
Oh, my goodness.
What is all that? Encyclopedia of Nazi War Criminals.
Which apparently includes Veronica's dad.
After World War II, surviving Nazis fled around the world.
I'm not an accountant, but looks like Peter Vandenberg got rich cleaning
their dirty money.
Yeah, and apparently Veronica took over right where he left off, using his
criminal network.
But I don't understand.
What does the Eye want us to do with this? Well, if I'm not mistaken, the
Eye wants us to unmask the Vandenbergs, bring down two generations of
criminals with a single sleight of hand.
I've read some interesting rumors about the Vandenbergs Online.
Looks like 15 years ago, Veronica's mom killed herself, and a week later,
their housekeeper's brakes failed.
Her car crashed.
She and her son died.
There was some suspicion of foul play, but nothing was ever proven.
Oh,
hold on, hold on, hold on.
Listen closely.
Split up.
Find a way out.
Okay. Go, go, go.
He's right.
Everybody split up.
Turn around.
You heard it, Bosco.
Here they come.
It.
Sorry. Bonjour.
Bonjour. You know, normally, I like to give a proper tour to new guests.
I suspect you've discovered that this house holds many secrets.
Thaddeus.
Thaddeus. Would you like to see a magic trick, Sekou? So how about if I make
myself disappear?
There.
Hurry. This way, that is.
Oh, thank God.
Hey, which is the fastest way out of here? Around this bend.
Yeah, There's a passageway.
Just follow the cream through the forest.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This can't be happening.
Come on, Thaddeus, stand up.
We're gonna go now.
We need to get you help.
Please, stand up.
You have to stop Veronica Vanderburg.
We can't do it without you, Thaddeus.
You don't need me.
But you do need each other.
Never.
I knew when I came here, this was probably my final trick.
No. Don't let me die in vain.
There's work to be done.
Go. Go now.
Go. Please, before us.
We gotta go.
The police took June into custody.
Well, what about Jack and Mary? Them two? Okay, so we break him out.
Well, let's just talk about this for a second.
What? Listen to me.
We need to be smart.
No, we gotta get my friend out of jail.
Look, when you were researching all that stuff about us, you know what
didn't come up? Charlie, and June are my only friends.
You know what I really love about them? They don't make me feel like an
asshole. I'm getting you.
Bosco, listen to me.
Hey. What? One second.
Listen to me.
You can't.
Why tell me? They're looking for you, Bosco.
They're looking for all of us.
Yes. Yes.
You're gonna get arrested, too.
Yes. Shit.
Exactly. If only there was somebody else crazy enough to stage a jailbreak
with no resources, no protection atlas.
Yeah, maybe there is.
Thaddeus Marcus Bradley.
In case you're interested in the name of the man you just murdered.
Ah, yes.
That was unfortunate.
You know, when this whole thing started, I didn't give a shit about you or
your diamond.
But you just went and made it deeply personal.
And now I am really looking forward to taking you down.
My father would have loved you.
He was quite fond of magic.
When I was 5 or 6, in one of the few moments that I had him to myself, he
taught me a trick.
He would make a red silk handkerchief disappear and then come back out of
his mouth.
I loved.
Had just the right amount of flair.
And I practiced that trick for months.
I thought that if I could do it just right, I would earn more of him.
But that was the illusion.
I've hated magic ever since.
The camp, the cheese.
Not to say anything of con artists like you with your mentalism.
Neither one of us has psychic powers, Mr.
McKinney. You don't have to.
You know where my heart is.
And I don't have to because you're going to tell me.
I think you're smart enough to know that I ain't telling you shit.
As we say it, Texas.
And you're wrong about mentalism.
People wear their entire life story on their face.
You just have to know how to read it.
Take yours, for example.
May I? With pleasure.
This is gonna be fun.
Well, you've already shared in excruciating detail your daddy issues, but
I'm curious about your mom.
Why did she commit suicide? Was she as desperate for your father's attention
as you were? Oh, she was.
And why was that? Did your father give his attention to someone else? When
you tuck your hair behind your ear, that's a tell.
He was.
So was he banging his secretary? No, that's too cliche.
But it had to be someone close to your mom for her.
To a good friend.
Hairdresser. It wasn't the housekeeper, was it? No.
Not the housekeeper.
I don't have time for this.
And that's what people usually say when I'm Getting hot.
Should we crank up the ac? Maybe open a window? Now, if my dad was having
sex with my housekeeper and my mom found out and committed suicide, I
probably wouldn't and cut the brakes on my housekeeper's car.
But then again, I'm not a psychopath.
You are a sad and pathetic man.
I can see why you want to end it.
Hey, Veronica.
You know, walking away is also a tell.
Come on.
If you don't.
Bonsoir.
It's pretty disgusting, even for you.
I think I may have overdone it on the wine.
Hi, Lola.
You look great, by the way.
Okay. I didn't think I'd ever see you again.
How'd you find us? A little bird.
You told me.
Imagine my surprise.
You guys all got back together without me.
What? No, it's not like that.
You don't understand.
Oh, was it? No.
You're Free Dick.
The cavalry.
Miss me? A lot.
Oh, hello there.
It's me, Lula.
Teeth. Lula.
Remember? I too was once a Horseman.
Yeah, I asked about you.
I was the only one.
You were the.
He was the only one.
Really hurt.
And move.
We have to get to the.
Meet him.
Okay, okay, here's a plan.
I have the getaway car.
It's all ready to go.
I just need Jack to hotwire it.
Your plan is for me to steal the car? Uh huh.
Okay. I'll hot wire the car, you get tuned.
Do not leave without it.
All right.
Meet us outside.
Okay. Oh.
Watch for flashing lights.
Okay. You know, I can hot wire them.
You can let go of me now.
Right, sorry.
Come here.
Where is the diamond? Thank you.
Got your back, you know.
But who's got yours? Flashing lights.
Run.
Look into my eyes Watch and wonder why I whisper words of weak in your will
and sleep.
Not everyone's acceptable.
I said,
is it a super play?
Hello? Jack.
You know, you could have told us you were coming at a police car.
Thank you very much.
And look, we made the fifth Horseman reappear.
Hello? Lula.
Hi. Okay.
Are you okay? Yeah, no, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
But they have merit.
Yeah, I escaped.
He. He couldn't.
Yeah, yeah, very emotional time for everybody here.
Clearly a lot going on.
I'm. I'm really trying not to take any of this personally, but please,
please, can you tell me, did the eye contact you directly? Yeah.
You too? Yes.
Well, why didn't you call me sooner? I'm so sorry.
I had to find a babysitter.
Everything happened like that.
Wait, sorry.
You two know each other? Yeah, we know how many female magicians do you
think there are in the world? I.
The fact there are three of us in the room right now, it's, like, shocking.
Mind blown.
That's true.
I'm surprised the universe isn't folding in on itself.
Exactly. Abu Dhabi.
Just do that.
Sorry, I didn't.
I'm a big fan of yours, by the way.
I was trying to figure out where Veronica was going to be next, and
apparently Vanderburg Global has a motorsports team.
They're introducing a new car this weekend in Abu Dhabi.
So we can get Merit back and expose her.
No, no, no.
I am not exposing her.
I am not exposing anyone, okay? I don't care what the Eye wants.
No, we are swapping this for Merit, and then we are done.
We're saving our friends.
We're not saving the world.
Then what? We just go back to our lives and let her walk away? After Russia,
you said magicians are entertainers, not superheroes.
And I'm starting to think that you were right.
She doesn't just launder money like her father.
You saw what happened at Thaddeus.
Obviously, I'm playing a bit of catch up here.
Right? I don't have all of the information, but I don't think that that
should stop me from having an opinion about what we do next.
Exactly. No, it shouldn't.
Atlas and I think we should expose Vanessa.
Veronica. Veronica.
For murder and what is laundering and for money laundering.
For murder and for money laundering.
Tie her up.
No. No.
It is too dangerous.
And Atlas is right.
What? We are done sacrificing ourselves.
I'm sorry.
It's not worth it.
That's bullshit.
What? You're wrong.
Am I sorry? No, don't be sorry.
Say it.
You are.
You're wrong.
It's just, before I discovered the Horsemen, I didn't give a shit about
anything. My family gave me up.
I hated the whole world.
And then I saw a video of you guys, and you were trying to make the world
less corrupt, less terrible.
And that made me give a shit.
So what's the trick?
I promise this is gonna work.
But is that enough misdirection? As long as she's here and not there, we can
take care of that.
If you're even just five minutes late.
Five? I'd say one.
One minute late.
How do we know enough people are gonna show up? You guys is already viral.
I guarantee there'll be a crowd.
This is nuts.
There's too many variables.
Hey, we'll be in constant contact with you if something goes awry.
Yeah, there's like no margin for error here, man.
Okay? Zero.
We are going to have to be absolutely flawless if we're going to pull
something this risky off with this many moving parts in this ridiculously
short amount of time.
Okay? Yes.
Yeah. But speaking for myself, at least I think the seven of us have a
better chance than most.
Would you look at this? When did the great Boscolaroi go soft? Okay, guys,
are we doing this or What? Is a 10 million to one shot? Those are my kind of
odds.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The time has come.
Tonight, for one night only.
Come in close.
Closer. Cuz the more you think you see, the easier it'll be to fool you.
The countdown begins.
In only two hours, the Four Horsemen will be on stage together for the first
time in 10 years.
J. Daniel Atlas.
Henley Reeves,
Jack Wilder
And Luma May.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The Four Horsemen.
That's right, the Horsemen are back.
For one night only.
Last week we stole the Heart Diamond.
And tonight, in two hours time, we're gonna return it to its rightful owner.
All of you.
You think that got her attention? If that didn't, I don't know what will.
All right, listen.
Now that you know how bad things can actually get, can you please just try
playing it safe this one time? No.
Okay. Oh, here she is.
Right on time.
You enjoying the show? It's a little tacky for my taste.
I assume you chose your venue for its proximity to my own.
Well, good news for you.
I've placed you on our guest list.
Bring me my heart.
We'll make an exchange.
Mr. McKinney for the diamond.
Outside, under the lights and not the first hint of magic.
One rabbit comes out of a hat, One ace slides out of a sleeve.
And your friend goes poof.
Just trying to use pollen so you'll understand.
Welcome to the W.
Yas island, the Orlando of the Middle East.
Now, finally, thank you to Yas island for hosting an event worthy of the
fastest team in motorsport.
This track is elite.
But it will soon provide our competitors with the most common view in
racing. The rear wings of our cars.
Holy shit, that's Veronica.
She has a very commanding presence.
Our magical friends have arrived.
Why don't you go and greet them? Thank you so much for coming.
I hope you enjoy the race.
Okay, Atlas said to create a distraction.
How are we going to pull this off? There is security everywhere.
Okay, you guys, calm down.
I got this.
Hello? Hi.
David. Cool.
I'm from Media Relations.
I was just checking in.
Do you think you guys could do a different camera placement? Okay, thanks.
Continue your turn.
Let's do this.
Make sure you confirm the authenticity of the diamond.
These people are very tricky.
I'm so glad you came.
What did you say? We bury the hatchet in each other's necks? He's funny.
We each possess something beneficial to the other.
Perfect reason to do business.
Only there's one caveat.
I fervently hope our mutual dealings are.
Out of clothes.
She's so poor.
I hate her.
How's it going? Well, can I help you? Yeah, we're here to shoot the car, I
think. Oh, right.
Of course.
Obviously. There you are, you.
It's my jacket.
Somewhere. There it is.
We're with checkered flags.
The DOC Series.
Next season's on Vandenberg Motorsports.
It seriously didn't give you guys a heads up? Typical.
We're just gonna get some inserts, maybe some B roll.
And some party people gawking at this beauty.
All right, whenever you're ready.
All right.
Don't touch the car.
We gotta shoot the interior.
Yeah, I can actually get you a cameo in this thing.
Save it.
I've got my orders.
Yeah, and so do we.
Good evening, Ms.
Vanderberg. Yeah, we're trying to get that footage you asked for, but we ran
into a little bit of a problem.
You're going to be in trouble.
She wants to talk to you.
It's not good.
My guy.
Not good.
Hello. Listen, my father always said no imp sat unseen.
And at this very moment, my car is the diamond.
So you can either let them do their job or you can find yourself a new one.
Sorry for the.
Hold on, man.
You're good.
You're the best.
You could just back up for me really quick, just for the light.
Thanks, man.
Well, shall we get on with it, please? Oh, of course.
You have a goon.
Forgive me.
Come on.
You don't trust us? After all we've been through?
Is there a problem? Double check if you're not certain it's the heart.
Yes, of course it is.
Now, please, can you get our friend.
Come on.
There he is.
Okay. Hey.
You okay? Well, now that I know I'm worth half a billion.
I still think we got ripped off.
But it's good to see you.
Signed, sealed, delivered.
See? I'm a woman of my word.
Stick around if you want.
Enjoy the party.
What a God's name.
Come on.
How do you make this thing go? How? They know I can't concentrate with you
yelling at me?
Excuse me?
You join the show.
You just got to stand there, Ging, or get my car back.
You did this.
Okay, here we go.
Okay. Atlas, you wanted a distraction, you got a distraction.
And this thing's tail hatch,
we fell through trap door or something.
Is everybody okay? Where are.
When I woke up this morning, there was only one thing I wanted more than my
diamond. My horseman under lock and key.
And now that I have both, I must admit, I'm feeling a little bit spoiled.
While you were prepping your little performance, I curated a trick of my
own. Five Horsemen, trapped.
No escape.
You five may be national treasures, but we have those here, too.
Only they're hard to find because they're buried inside.
To the world, it will appear you died in a failed escape act.
Now, let's see some magic.
Magic. Somebody call for backup.
Jack, call June.
Anyone have service? God.
She must have scrambled the cell signal.
She thought of everything.
Hula. Whose side are you on? I'm on our side, obviously.
But she also thought of everything.
Both things can be true at one time.
Sand is getting higher.
Sand's getting bigger.
There's more sand.
And it's getting larger.
Henley. Henley.
First principle of escape.
How long is this Survivable? Right.
Okay, great.
Judging from the rate of the flow, the volume of the box.
Yeah, we're screwed.
Oh, amazing.
Okay, how about the second principle of escape then? Okay, so that's the box
itself. Is there a flaw? Is there a weakness? There a back door? Everybody
just decent check.
Seal, seal, seal, seal.
Everything sealed.
Each answer.
The third principle.
I have what you're after.
Perfect. I will meet you where the heart resides.
I can hardly wait.
Straight to the vault.
No, no, no, no.
Yes. Help me, Ricky Bobby.
Help me.
Is this really gonna happen right now? We're just gonna die here? Here in
this box? Really? It's funny.
A week ago, I wanted to die, and.
And then I get my reason to live back, and now we're actually going to die.
How? How.
How is that funny? Well, I mean, it was funnier in my head.
It's. You know, it's peculiar.
Funny. No, no.
We're out of options.
God, I never should have been that horrible about your website and your
costumes and the logo is not embarrassing that the eye and Wilder is a
little magic wand.
It's not.
It's cute and it's charming and I missed you.
Listen, I know I don't always show it, but I really do think the world of
all of you.
Cannot believe we're getting buried alive.
I mean, it's like a Westerner.
Wait, wait.
Buried alive? That's like an old magic tradition.
Sorry, who.
Who do we know who did that.
Bill Shurick nearly died doing that.
Remember, he got into a plexiglass coffin and had it covered in sand.
In the plexiglass break, the sand got wet.
Sand got wet.
I remember now.
It rained the night before it.
Wet sand is heavier than dry.
It broke the glass.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
If we broke that pipe, then it would wet the sand, and then it'll.
It'll break the box, right? If I could, I could wrap something around it.
I might be able to get some leverage.
Okay, Mayor, give me your belt.
Okay, okay.
You got it, you got it.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Lock this.
Come on.
This, come on.
Help me.
Pull me down.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Pull over.
We have you surrounded.
I'd love to pull over, but I'm finally getting the head.
I did it.
I'm the greatest driver in the world.
No, no, no, no.
Watch out.
Turn off the engine and exit the vehicle.
We've got you surrounded.
Put your hands up and don't move.
I'm sorry.
Did I forget to use my blinker? You're under arrest.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Excellent work.
We've had a red notice.
Juan Bosco.
Leroy. Thank you.
No problem.
Yep. Atlas is going to kill me.
Why? Is coming into too fast and the glass won't break.
I. All this for a diamond? Could use that now.
Nothing cuts glass like a diamond.
Wait, wait.
Henley. Henley.
Yeah. I can hold my breath for eight minutes.
If anyone can get us out of this, we can.
We're crossing into the desert.
Mount Dust Storm is getting worse.
What's he doing here? Ms.
Vanderberg's diamond.
That you and your friend stole.
Something.
That was fun.
It's working.
It.
Way to go.
All right.
We gotta show the catch.
Hope we're not too late.
Identity verified.
You made it.
Do you have what I want? If you have what I want,
where's the evidence?
Right here.
I'm the evidence.
Ador. You did.
Now you see me.
It's quite fascinating the things people do to make something or someone
disappear.
Ah.
I taught you that trick.
Just like our father taught you.
And now, after 15 years, you're.
You're trying to ruin me.
No. All 15 years I didn't know you'd be in that car.
But you must have been relieved to hear.
I was.
When we hit the water, I couldn't unbuckle my seat belts.
Mom freed me with her dying breath.
I had nothing but fondness for you, Charlie.
Let me finally treat you like a brother.
I am your Brother.
Father's blood is in both of us.
Though he'd never acknowledge man, God knows Mother begged.
And the shame drove my mother to her grave.
Then you sent man to hers.
Fine. You're right.
It should be yours.
Was. Here.
Take it.
Bullet catch.
It's impossible.
No. Just magic.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you.
All right, thank you.
Earlier tonight, J janu Atlas promised to return the Heart diamond to its
rightful owner.
But before we do that, some introductions are in order.
First, let's say hello to the fierce force of nature, the extraordinary June
Br.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
And give it up for the indomitable Bosco Loy.
The pleasure is ours.
Hello, gorgeous.
And of course, we could not have done any of this in the first place without
the help of the world's greatest magicians.
The four.
Sorry. Make that five.
Horsewen.
Thank you, everyone.
Wow. You know, we have entertained, well dazzled audiences all over the
world, but we have never been part of a trick like this.
And you may be asking yourself, how did they pull this off? Okay, well,
every magician needs an assistant.
Veronica. You may think Veronica here as Peter Vanderburgh's sole heir, is
the the rightful owner of this diamond.
But here's the twist.
Peter didn't have one child.
He had two.
That's right.
And that other child cheated death and landed in New York City,
where vengeance became his life's work.
But he would need help.
So he.
He recruited,
enticed and lord, some of the most brilliant minds he could assemble, laying
the groundwork for a trick unlike any other.
Which brings us to tonight.
Make some noise for the mastermind behind all of this, our best friend.
A ghost until this very moment.
Charlie Vanderberg.
You know, I said I'd enjoy taking you down, but this is more fun than I
anticipate. You are still a sad, empathetic man.
And you are nothing.
Oh, hold on, everyone.
One sec.
And you never will be.
I don't understand how you pulled this off.
You don't understand? Veronica doesn't seem to understand how she found
herself in this position.
Well, let's explain it to her.
You see, the finest magic preys on assumptions that the car waiting for you
was the same one that dropped you off.
Let's go.
That in act of Mother nature sure is nothing but.
And that a vault in the desert isn't just smoke and mirrors.
That a gun isn't filled with blanks.
And that an elevator is just simply descending into Earth.
If you want to trick the master of deception, you have to manipulate her.
Reality. And for our last trick, why don't we make Veronica disappear?
You don't win.
I demand you.
There she is.
Missing her already.
Find final reveal.
The real Veronica Vanderburg.
The world is full of illusions.
One of the biggest is that this diamond belongs to the Vandenbergs at all.
As my father's only unincarcerated next of kin, I'll make sure every one of
our illicit buyers faces legal repercussions.
And then I'll gift all our assets, including the heart, to the South African
communities they came from.
With a few extra dollars left for all of you.
Forceful crowds always leave with deeper pockets.
Nice trick.
I learned from the best.
Thank you.
Thank you for joining us.
All of us.
And please remember, no matter what cards life deals you, you have to learn
to make your own magic.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are the Horsemen.
Sa.
All right, what do you want? Pomegranate or boysenberry? Dude, I said I
wanted a drink.
Let's give it a try.
Kids today.
Of course.
That's pretty good.
I'm trying now.
I think you dropped this.
Oh. Card.
Just in case you want to frame it.
Thanks. I might.
You know, I still cannot believe you're a Vanderburg.
Neither could she.
I was thinking.
I feel like we should start our own group.
You guys.
Girls. Magic group.
Yes. Horse girls.
No. Horse women.
Not that.
Ladies of the horse ponies.
Really bad.
Can I talk to you real quick? Not trying to infiltrate the horsewomen.
What's up?
It's just.
Speak. What is the matter with you? It's hard because I don't.
I don't know how you feel, so.
Hey, everybody.
Everybody, come on over here, please.
Yeah. Come on, guys.
Hey, can you grab some more of those delicious things? Posco? Chad, you are
gonna love this stuff.
It is flaps.
No merit.
Please. It slaps.
What I meant to say is.
It's good.
Yeah, right? Yes.
And I will be the one to say it.
I am going to miss you guys.
I was just thinking the same thing.
Yeah, me, too.
Damn it.
I love you guys.
We love you, too.
We love you.
You, too.
Wow. Very sweet.
Even me? Really? You must be very drunk.
Whoa.
Go back to what? We all love each other.
Go back to that.
You guys expecting someone? No one's supposed to know where we are.
Who's it from? Doesn't say.
Open it.
You open it.
Okay.
Oh, that's the.
That's the thing from the door.
Yeah, from the chateau.
Do you.
You mind if I take another crack at it? Yeah, go for it.
Yeah, I think I can handle it this time.
Hello, Horseman.
Did you miss me? Dylan.
But he's supposed to be imprisoned.
I know what you're thinking.
He lied to us.
But I.
I didn't lie to you.
I just led you to believe something that wasn't true.
But it was for your own good.
Trust me.
There's more to this mystery than you realize.
And the end result is that the Horsemen are back together again.
It warms my heart.
Now for you three imposters.
Brazenly pretending like you're part of our top secret organization.
You think you're gonna get away with it with no consequences or
repercussions. Well, you thought right.
Welcome. Welcome to the Eye.
As for the rest of you, you thought your work was done.
Thank you, Genti.
You're just getting stone.
What's the trick.